<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>djworth</title><link>https://danworth.com/</link><description>Recent content on djworth</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>[Home](/) &amp;#183; Theme [Simpleness](https://github.com/RainerChiang/simpleness) Powered by [Hugo](https://gohugo.io/)</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 18:45:26 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://danworth.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Projects</title><link>https://danworth.com/projects/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 18:45:31 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://danworth.com/projects/</guid><description>I have a lot of projects in different states of being unfinished. This page is designed for me to start cleaning up these projects and publishing them mainly for my own peace of mind.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://danworth.com/about/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 18:45:26 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://danworth.com/about/</guid><description>Who Am I? I&amp;rsquo;m a Dad to two wonderful kids trying to figure out the world of middle school. I&amp;rsquo;m a Husband to my high school sweetheart ❤️. We have two American Bulldogs Brutus and Ada. Both dogs are rescues Brutus is more of a traditional rescue where we adopted him from the American Bulldog Rescue he was 1.5 years old when we adopted him. Now Ada (named after the cryptocurrency Ada on the Cardano network) we &amp;ldquo;rescued&amp;rdquo; her because the person that bought her could no longer keep Ada in their apartment.</description></item><item><title>My New Hugo Site</title><link>https://danworth.com/posts/my-new-hugo-site/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 18:37:10 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://danworth.com/posts/my-new-hugo-site/</guid><description>Hello World My name is Dan Worth and you can read more about me @ the about page.
Let&amp;rsquo;s see how this goes I, like many in my profession have tried to maintain a website/blog but rarely keep it updated. This is my attempt to have a place where I&amp;rsquo;ll actually post things I&amp;rsquo;m working on or thinking about to help me flesh out my ideas and thoughts.
I like Golang so naturally I picked Hugo as my static site generator.</description></item></channel></rss>